goqii.com 2019-04-03

# Welcome to GOQii Life

#### Our Policy

* We, GOQii (collectively used to refer to GOQii Inc., GOQii Technologies Pvt. Ltd. and its affiliates, successors and assigns) bring to you a digital health and fitness subscription service that combines one-on-one mobile personal coaching and fitness tracking technology to help you shift to a healthier lifestyle and reach your goals. While fitness trackers and apps are useful tools, they are missing the elements of on-going engagement, motivation and accountability. GOQii solves this by connecting your activity tracker or smart watch to a professional health and fitness coach of your choice via the “GOQii App” (available on iOS and Android) and a wearable GOQii fitness band (" **GOQii Tracker** "). You can read more about GOQii and our product at website [goqii.com](https://goqii.com/) (together with the GOQii App is hereby referred to as the " **Platform** "). For ease of reading and clarity, the Platform, the GOQii App and the GOQii Tracker are collectively referred to as the " **Services** ". Your use of the Platform and Services are governed by the Terms of Use and other policies of GOQii.

We know that the privacy of your personal data is very important to you. This Privacy Policy sets forth GOQii’s policy with respect to information including personally identifiable data (" **Personal Data** ") and other information that is collected from Platform visitors and users.

#### Information We Collect

* When you interact with us through the Platform and Services, we may collect Personal Data and other information from you, as further described below:

#### Personal Data

  * We collect Personal Data from you when you voluntarily provide such information, such as when you contact us with inquiries, collect, store or transfer data using the GOQii Band, post information or comments, respond to one of our surveys or questionnaires, register for access to GOQii Services, allow us to access your location information (such as by using the GPS on your mobile device or the GOQii Band), or use certain GOQii Services or access the Platform. This Privacy Policy is applicable to our collection of Personal Data through all of the abovementioned means.

The kind of Personal data that we collect may include such as your full name, email address, password, gender, profile picture, contact details, address, date of birth, height, weight, diet and digestive information, fitness and exercise details, medical history and conditions and medication details

By voluntarily providing us with Personal Data, you are consenting to our use of it, in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If you provide Personal Data to us, you acknowledge and agree that such Personal Data may be transferred from your current location to the offices and servers of GOQii and the authorized third parties referred to herein located in worldwide.

#### Non-Identifiable Data

  * When you interact with GOQii through the Platform, we receive and store certain personally non-identifiable information. Such information, which is collected passively using various technologies, cannot presently be used to specifically identify you. Consequently, we do not adjust or alter our Platform’s automatic tracking and data collection in response to a Do Not Track signal or request. GOQii may store such non-identifiable information itself or such information may be included in databases owned and maintained by GOQii affiliates, agents or service providers. This Platform may use such information and pool it with other information to track, for example, the total number of visitors to our Platform, the number of visitors to each page of our Platform, and the domain names of our visitors' Internet service providers. It is important to note that no Personal Data is available or used in this process.

In operating this Platform, we may use a technology called "cookies." A cookie is a piece of information that the computer that hosts our Platform gives to your browser when you access the Platform. Our cookies help provide additional functionality to the Platform and help us analyze Platform usage more accurately. For instance, our Platform may set a cookie on your browser that allows you to access the Platform without needing to remember and then enter a password more than once during a visit to the Platform. In all cases in which we use cookies, we will not collect Personal Data except with your permission. On most web browsers, you will find a “help” section on the toolbar. Please refer to this section for information on how to receive notification when you are receiving a new cookie and how to turn cookies off. We recommend that you leave cookies turned on because they allow you to take advantage of some of the Platform’s features.

his Platform may enable the use of the Adobe Flash Player. Adobe’s Flash Player is used by the vast majority of websites that offer video and other interactive content. By default, your use of the Adobe Flash Player generates “flash cookies” (also known as “persistent identification elements” or “local shared objects”). The Adobe Flash Player (and similar applications) use flash cookies to remember user settings, preferences and usage similar to the browser cookies referenced above. You can disable, delete and control the degree to which you accept flash cookies by accessing your Adobe Flash Player management tools directly through the settings manager for Adobe Flash, located here. If you do not allow flash cookies to take any disc space on your computer, you may not be able to take advantage of or participate in certain features on this Platform.

  * #### Aggregated Personal Data

In an ongoing effort to better understand and serve the users of GOQii Services, GOQii may conduct research on its customer demographics and behavior based on the Personal Data and other information provided to us. This research may be compiled and analyzed on an aggregate basis, and GOQii may share this aggregate data with its affiliates, agents and business partners. This aggregate information does not identify you personally. GOQii may also disclose aggregated user statistics in order to describe our services to current and prospective business partners, and to other third parties for other lawful purposes.

#### Location Information

  * Our Service may collect and use your location information (for example, by requesting your location in your profile or by using the GPS on your mobile device or the GOQii Band) to provide certain functionality of our Service. We may use your location information in conjunction with your Personal Data or in an aggregate way, as described above in the “Aggregated Personal Data” section.

#### Our Use of Your Personal Data and Other Information

* GOQii uses the Personal Data you provide in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy. If you provide Personal Data for a certain reason, we may use the Personal Data in connection with the reason for which it was provided. For instance, if you contact us by e-mail, we will use the Personal Data you provide to answer your question or resolve your problem. Also, if you provide Personal Data in order to obtain access to GOQii Services, we will use your Personal Data to provide you with access to such services, in conjunction with such services and to monitor your use of such services. GOQii, its subsidiaries and affiliates (the “GOQii Related Companies”) may also use your Personal Data and other personally non-identifiable information collected through the Platform to help us improve the content and functionality of the Platform, to better understand our users and to improve GOQii Services. GOQii and its Related Companies may use this information to contact you in the future by using multiple communication channels to tell you about services we believe will be of interest to you. Email communication we send you will contain instructions permitting you to "opt-out" of receiving future communications. SMS/IVR communication that is sent to you can be opted out by writing an email to [support@goqii.com](mailto:support@goqii.com) & mentioning what you would like to opt out of.

In addition, if at any time, you wish not to receive any future communications whatsoever or you wish to have your name deleted from our mailing lists, please contact us at [support@goqii.com](mailto:support@goqii.com). 

If GOQii intends on using any Personal Data in any manner that is not consistent with this Privacy Policy, you will be informed of such anticipated use prior to or at the time at which the Personal Data is collected.

#### Our Disclosure of Your Personal Data and Other Information

* GOQii is not in the business of selling your information. We consider this information to be a vital part of our relationship with you. There are, however, certain circumstances in which we may share your Personal Data with certain third parties without further notice to you, as set forth below: 

#### Business Transfers 

  * As we develop our business, we might sell or buy businesses or assets. In the event of a corporate sale, merger, reorganization, dissolution or similar event, Personal Data may be part of the transferred assets.

#### Related Companies 

  * We may also share your Personal Data with our Related Companies for purposes consistent with this Privacy Policy.

#### Agents, Consultants and Related Third Parties 

  * GOQii, like many businesses, sometimes hires other companies to perform certain business-related functions. Examples of such functions include mailing information, maintaining databases and processing payments. When we employ another company to perform a function of this nature, we only provide them with the information that they need to perform their specific function.

#### Legal Requirements 

  * GOQii may disclose your Personal Data, if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to (i) comply with a legal obligation, (ii) protect and defend the rights or property of GOQii, (iii) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of the Platform or the public, (iv) protect against legal liability.

#### Other Third Parties

  * We may also disclose your Personal Data with third party service providers such as Eco-System Partners, insurance companies, data analytics companies, marketing and research companies for use of such information including for offering additional services either bundled with, or in addition to the Services, or to assist GOQii in providing the Services to you. We will share such information with Insurance companies only when the customers have specifically authorized before buying the services/insurance product.

#### Your Choices:

* You can use the Platform without providing any Personal Data. If you choose not to provide any Personal Data, you may not be able to use certain GOQii Services.

#### Exclusions

* This Privacy Policy does not apply to any Personal Data collected by GOQii other than Personal Data collected through the Services. This Privacy Policy shall not apply to any unsolicited information you provide to GOQii through this Platform or through any other means. This includes, but is not limited to, information posted to any public areas of the Platform (collectively, “Public Areas”), any ideas for new products or modifications to existing products, and other unsolicited submissions (collectively, “Unsolicited Information”). All Unsolicited Information shall be deemed to be non-confidential and GOQii shall be free to reproduce, use, disclose, and distribute such Unsolicited Information to others without limitation or attribution.

#### Third Parties and Links to Other Web Sites

* This Privacy Policy applies only to the Platform and to the services provided. We do not permit third parties to collect Personal Data on our Platform, but our Platform may contain links to other web sites not operated or controlled by GOQii (the " **Third Party Sites** "). The policies and procedures we described here do not apply to the Third Party Sites. The links from this Platform do not imply that GOQii endorses or has reviewed the Third Party Sites. We suggest contacting those sites directly for information on their privacy policies.

#### Social Media

* GOQii may allow you to choose to access certain social media websites and services that are owned and/or controlled by third parties (like Facebook and Twitter) (such websites and services, collectively, the “Social Media Services”) through the Platform. If you elect to access and use the Social Media Services, you will be sharing your information (which may include personal data if you elect to share such information) with those Social Media Services. As with other Third Party Sites, the information that you share with the Social Media Services will be governed by the privacy policies and terms of service of the providers of such Social Media Services and not by the policies and procedures we describe here. When you add Social Media Service accounts to GOQii Services or log into the Platform using your Social Media Services account, we will collect relevant information necessary to enable the Platform to access that Social Media Service. As part of such integration, the Social Media Service will provide GOQii with access to certain information that you have provided to such Social Media Service, and we will use, store and disclose such information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. However, please remember that the manner in which Social Media Services use, store and disclose your information is governed by the policies of the applicable Social Media Services provider and, as a result, GOQii shall not have any liability or responsibility for the privacy practices or other actions of Social Media Services that may be enabled within and/or otherwise accessible through the Platform.

You may also have the option of posting your Services activities to Social Media Services when you access content through the Services (for example, you may post to Facebook that you performed an activity on the Service); you acknowledge that if you choose to use this feature, your friends, followers and subscribers on any Social Media Services you have enabled will be able to view such activity.

#### Security

* GOQii takes reasonable steps to protect the Personal Data provided via the Platform and the Services from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. We have adopted reasonable security practices and procedure, as further described in our information security policy, available with our CTO to ensure that the Personal Data collected is secure. You agree that such measures are secure and adequate. While we will endeavor to take all reasonable and appropriate steps to keep secure any information which we hold about you and prevent unauthorized access, you acknowledge that, no Internet or e-mail transmission or security measure is ever fully secure or error free. In particular, e-mail sent to or from this Platform may not be secure. Therefore, you should take special care in deciding what information you send to us via e-mail. Please keep this in mind when disclosing any Personal Data to GOQii via the Internet. We will not be liable in any way in relation to any breach of security or unintended loss or disclosure of information caused by us in relation to your Personal Data.

#### International Transfer

* Your information may be transferred to, and / or maintained on servers located outside of your state, province or country. Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.

#### Other Terms and Conditions

* Your access to and use of this Platform is subject to the Terms of Service. 

#### Changes to GOQii’s Privacy Policy

* The Platform and our business may change from time to time. As a result, at times, it may be necessary for GOQii to make changes to this Privacy Policy. GOQii reserves the right to update or modify this Privacy Policy at any time and from time to time without prior notice. Please review this policy periodically, and especially before you provide any Personal Data. This Privacy Policy was last updated on the date indicated above. Your continued use of the Platform after any changes or revisions to this Privacy Policy shall indicate your agreement with the terms of such revised Privacy Policy.

#### Access to Information and Contacting GOQii

* You may change or update information in your profile, or delete your account entirely. To keep your Personal Data accurate, current, and complete, please update your profile or contact us as specified below. We will take reasonable steps to update or correct Personal Data in our possession that you have previously submitted via this Platform or the Service.

Please also feel free to contact us, if you have any questions about GOQii’s Privacy Policy or the information practices of this Platform.

#### Withdrawal of Personal Data

* Further, you will have the option to not provide your consent, or withdraw any consent given earlier, provided that the decision to not provide consent / withdrawal of the consent is intimated to us in writing. If you do not provide us Personal Data or withdraw the consent to provide us with any of your Personal Data at any point in time, we shall have the option not to provide the benefits for the purpose of which the said Personal Data was sought. 

#### Authorization

* You authorize us to collect, store, process, transfer, share, part with your Personal Data, across borders and from your country and jurisdiction to any other countries and jurisdictions across the world (including India), with our affiliates / agent / third party service provider / partners and other agencies for purposes specified under this Privacy Policy or as may be required by law.

#### We May Update this Agreement

* These terms of this Privacy Policy may change. Because your use of GOQii Health Service means you agree to these Terms, if we revise and update these Terms, your continued use of GOQii Health Service will mean that you accept those changes. You choose whether or not you use GOQii Health Service. If you do not agree to all of these Terms, please do not use GOQii Health Service.

You may contact us as follows: [support@goqii.com](mailto:support@goqii.com)

#### Grievance Officer

* If you find any discrepancies or have any grievances in relation to the processing of information under this Privacy Policy, please contact us at: [support@goqii.com](mailto:support@goqii.com)

We will endeavor to respond within an appropriate timeframe.

#### Contacting Us

* We can address any questions, comments and concerns about our online privacy practices and policy. Please write to **Mr. Krishna Kumar** at [kk@goqii.com](mailto:kk@goqii.com).
